# # [ Drums Beating ]
# [ Continues ]
# [ Ends ]
# # [ Flute : Somber Melody ]
# [ Continues ]
# [ Ends ]
- Have you fallen asleep ? - [ French Accent ] Oh , I 'm sorry .
- I think you must be in love or something . - [ Footsteps Approaching ]
Why does the old bitch pick on me ?
That 's the second time this week . I nearly told her what she could do with the job .
Hey , you asleep ?
That 's what I asked her .
She wants me to stay till 7 : 00 again .
[ Woman ] What polish are you putting on ?
- The usual one , madame . - Oh , I 'm fed up with it .
I feel like a change .
- Uh , give me Revlon 's Fire and Ice . - Oh , I 'll go and get it .
[ Whirring ]
- [ Clicks ] - [ Hair Dryer Whirring ]
[ Chattering ]
Madame Denise ?
Madame Denise , Mrs. Rendlesham wants Revlon Fire and Ice .
I don 't think there 's any left .
[ Chattering ]
Put this on . She 'll never know the difference .
# # [ Flute Ensemble : Jazz ]
[ Heels Clicking On Sidewalk ]
# [ Continues ]
Hello , darling . How about a bit of the other , then ?
[ Bus Engine Roars ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Plates Clattering ]
# [ Continues ]
# [ Ends ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Sighs ]
You can 't eat stuff like this .
Come on . I 'll take you to Wheeler 's . Okay ?
I have to get back .
Oh , we can have a — we can have a quick meal .
Come on .
I can 't . I 'll be late .
Well , just — just one thing .
No ?
I can 't .
[ Sighs ]
Well , good-bye .
Well , just a — just a minute . What about tonight ?
I 'm sorry , but I 'm busy tonight .
You really make me feel wanted .
Who 's the lucky boy ?
I 'm having dinner with my sister .
Is she a good cook ?
[ Chuckles ] I don 't know . I never thought about it .
Well , at least it can 't be any worse than fish and chips .
[ Chuckles ]
I think we are having rabbit .
Rabbit ? Oh .
I thought they 'd all been killed off .
- No . She has a friend — - A rabbit ?
No , I think the friend has rabbits .
Poor bunny . Well , what about tomorrow ?
- Tomorrow ? - Yeah . Let 's have dinner tomorrow .
I 'll meet you at the Hoop and Toy . You know , the pub along there .
About , uh , 7 : 00 ?
[ Chattering ]
[ Engine Starts ]
# # [ Flute : Somber Melody ]
# [ Fades ]
- Hello . - Hello .
Come along boy . Walkies . Walkies .
- [ Doorbell Rings ] - Walkies .
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Elevator Whirring ]
[ Plates Clinking ]
[ Chattering , Laughter In Distance ]
[ Chattering , Laughter ]
[ Woman ] Have a good day ?
- Darling ? - Yes .
- How was work ? - All right .
[ Sighs ] It 's close today .
- Are you still going away ? - Oh , darling , please don 't start that again .
- How long are you going for ? - I 've told you .
- Fortnight ? - Mind .
How long ?
Ten or 12 days .
No more than that ?
[ Chuckles ]
I heard such a funny story on the news this evening .
Does he have to leave his things in the bathroom ?
The minister of health — What 's his name ?
He found eels coming out of his sink .
It was on the television . Even the announcer was laughing .
Why does he put his toothbrush in my glass ?
Carol , please .
We must get this crack mended .
- What ? - [ Doorbell Rings ]
[ Door Closes ]
- Hello . - Hello .
You 're early . I didn 't expect you for hours .
I couldn 't live without you for another minute .
Idiot . Anyway , you said 8 : 30 . I haven 't even started yet .
There 's a marvelous story in this evening 's paper .
- It takes at least one hour . - Huh ?
Your rabbit . I 'm cooking it .
Look . " Bring to the boil . Skim and allow to simmer slowly for one and a half hours . "
Yes . Well , we 'll eat out tonight . I 'll take you out .
- Here . Look . Read that . - [ Bell Clanging ]
Oh , I know that . I saw it on television .
- That bloody bell . - [ Clanging Continues ]
Eels . [ Chuckles ]
Pity it wasn 't lobster though .
You never give me a chance to show you what a good cook I am .
- Well you can tell me over dinner . - [ Clanging Continues ]
You 'd think they 'd have something better to do than clang away like that all the time .
Hmm . It 's worse when they start doing it at midnight .
I wonder what they ring it for anyway . Perhaps they have wild parties .
- Maybe they 'll invite me sometime . - [ Chuckles ]
[ Clanging Stops ]
Go and put your best bib and tucker on . I feel like a spree .
Ah .
The beautiful younger sister .
Comment ca va ?
I thought you were eating in .
Aren 't you going to have dinner ?
Yes . I 'm going to have dinner .
- But not here . - No .
Not here .
[ Sighs ]
Pass me that brush , will you ? There 's a love .
Just because I go out once , there 's no need to start sulking .
- I 'm not sulking . - Hmm . Well , you 're not exactly smiling .
Come on . You 're not going in for the Miss World competition .
[ Elevator Whirs ]
Will we go and see the Leaning Tower of Pisa ?
I don 't think Cinderella likes me .
- Cinderella ? - The little sister .
Ah ' don 't be silly .
Well are we going to see the Leaning Tower of Pisa ?
She 's a bit strung-up , isn 't she ?
- She 's just sensitive . That 's all . - [ Chuckles ]
You can say that again . She should see a doctor .
- What do you mean ? - Nothing , nothing , nothing .
- No . You tell me what you meant by that . - Nothing . Let 's forget it .
You want to see the Leaning Tower of Pisa , we 'll see the bloody thing . Now let 's relax .
- We 're going to dinner aren 't we ? - Don 't always change the subject when you start talking like that . You hear ?
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Dripping Continues ]
[ Elevator Whirring ]
[ Whirring Stops ]
[ Clangs ]
[ Woman ] Come along , boy . Din-din .
Time for din-din .
Come along , boy . Lovely din-din .
[ Ticking ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Dog Barking In Distance ]
[ Barking Stops ]
[ Vehicle Passing ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
- [ Sister Laughing ] - [ Man ] Oh , come — [ Indistinct ]
[ Laughing Continues ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Sister Clearing Throat ]
[ Sister Breathing Heavily ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Moaning Continues ]
[ Moaning Intensifies ]
Oh !
[ Moaning Softly ]
[ Sighs ]
Mmm .
[ Ticking Continues ]
- [ Plates Clattering ] - [ Birds Chirping ]
[ Gasps ]
I 'm sorry .
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Plates Clattering ]
Oh , look . I 've got to run . I 've left something at the flat .
Well aren 't you going to drop me off ?
I 've got no time .
Mmm . That 's bloody hot . No , you — you 'll have to take a cab .
Uh , here .
Oh , here . Are you — Am I gonna see you tonight ?
Um —
l-I 'll ring you , hmm ?
I 'll ring you .
[ Elevator Clicks ]
[ Elevator Door Closes ]
[ Elevator Whirring ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
Hello , darling . How did you sleep ?
All right .
Is he going to stay here every night ?
[ Airplane Passing Overhead ]
I really don 't think it 's any concern of yours .
- [ Phone Rings ] - He 's married though .
- Darling , it 's my affair . - [ Ringing Continues ]
We all have to lead our own lives in the end , you know .
[ Ringing Continues ]
Well just don 't stand around like that . Go and answer the phone .
Can 't you see I 'm busy ?
[ Ringing Continues ]
- Hello ? - [ Man ] Miss Ledoux ?
Yes .
How much longer are you going to keep me waiting for the rent ?
Oh . You want my sister .
- Ah . I suppose she 's out . - No , no . She 's here .
- [ Footsteps Approaching ] - Just a moment .
- Who is it ? - The landlord .
Oh , damn . He would ring up today .
- Hello , yes ? - Miss Ledoux ?
- Look . I 'm terribly sorry — - I bet you are .
- Now look . How much longer are you going to keep me waiting ? - I promise —
- I 've had your promises before . - I promise you 'll have the money tomorrow .
That 's what you said a fortnight ago .
You 'll have the money tomorrow without fail .
- Look . ' fyou 're not going to play fair by — - My sister will bring it round to you .
- [ Man ] Not you ? - N-No .
I 'm going away on holiday .
[ Man ] Now look Miss Ledoux . This time I 've had just about —
She 'll bring it round to you tomorrow . I promise .
She better , Miss Ledoux . That 's all I can say .
[ Dial Tone ]
[ Grumbles ] Just the sound of his voice makes my flesh creep .
Money , money money . That 's all he ever thinks about .
Good heavens . I shall be late again .
# [ Piano : Scales ]
# [ Continues ]
[ Blow Dryers Whirring ]
[ Chattering ]
- Is Bridget about ? - Oh , she 's downstairs .
Oh .
[ Sobbing ]
[ Pigeons Cooing ]
Bridget .
What 's the matter ?
- Nothing . - Tell me .
[ Sniffles ] Nothing .
Just bloody men . Promise you the earth , and then —
- Oh , I could cut my throat . - Don 't talk like that .
I thought this one was different .
- Did he — - Oh , he was a pig . Forget him .
[ Sniffles ] Oh . Look at my eyes .
[ Woman On P.A. ] Will Miss Bridget please come to the salon .
Mrs. Prendergast has arrived .
I 'll tell you the sordid details later .
Oh , why are they so filthy ?
Don 't be upset .
[ Woman On P.A. ] Will Miss Bridget please come to the salon right away .
# # [ Jazz Ensemble ]
[ Horn Honks ]
# [ Continues ]
- [ Man ] Cheerio then . - [ Man # 2 ] See you later .
# [ Ends ]
[ Speaking , Garbled ]
- You 're joking . - No . You should have seen them .
They went for each other like those women wrestlers in Hamburg .
One , a big lady with bloody great charlies , tried to claw the other girl 's face .
Got her fist right down her throat . Two pints of bitter , please .
- [ Bartenders ] Two pints sir ? - [ Man ] Lesbians ?
No , no . They both fancied the same bloke . ' Should have his luck .
And then they started in with their teeth , rolling about on the floor .
It was like a madhouse . And I was the only mug who tried to prevent them .
I ought to have my head examined .
I wouldn 't have minded seeing it .
Feel free , anytime .
- I ended up — - [ Man ] Thank you .
My coat torn , my shirt covered with blood .
If you like that sort of thing , I 'll introduce you to my cousin .
- She 's a black belt . - Black belt ?
How did you get on ?
- What ? - [ Man # 2 ] What 's your cousin like ?
- [ Man # 1 ] Well how did you get on with Little Miss Muffet ? - [ Man # 2 ] She sounds fun .
- When ? - [ Man # 1 ] Well , I thought you were taking her out to dinner .
[ Man # 2 ] Your cousin — what 's she like ?
Is that the right time ?
- No , sir . - Oh , come on . Fill us in with the gripping details .
The gripping details are that she had dinner with her sister .
Well maybe you should try the sister .
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
Are you playing hard to get ?
I 've been waiting over an hour .
Wh — What for ?
Well not for Christmas .
We made a date . Remember ? We 're having supper tonight .
Oh , I forgot .
Oh .
Well next time you forget , maybe you 'll let me know .
It 's not that but —
Are you all right ?
You look —
I don 't know . You look sort of — sort of funny .
I don 't feel —
I mean , I don 't know .
Oh well anyway come on . Now I 've found you , let 's — let 's go and eat something .
- I 'm starving . - But it 's too late .
Look . Have — Have you been fired or something ?
# # [ Rhythmic Clicking ]
All right . Come on . I 'll take you home . Come on .
# # [ Clicking Continues ]
- # # [ Clicking Continues ] - # # [ Banjo ]
[ Chattering In Distance ]
[ Dog Barking In Distance ]
# [ Piano : Scales ]
- Listen , Carol . I — I — - [ Vehicle Approaching ]
- I don 't — - [ Horn Honks , Tires Screech ] - [ Driver ] Clumsy bitch !
For heaven 's sake .
- # # [ Up-tempo Jazz ] - Carol !
Carol !
# [ Continues ]
# [ Ends ]
[ Cheering On TV ]
[ Man On TV ] Dean doing a little illegal bit outside the ring ...
but a neat head butt there by Larsen ...
and over to the corner with Ray Hunter coming in .
Finally Rebel Ray Hunter comes in after Stedman the giant .
And Hunter turning Stedman all over the place now but he ...
still exchanged places with Larsen .
And Larsen again for Hunter . And now it 's Hunter in again against Stedman .
Hunter really throwing Stedman around . I don 't know why he goes out .
And it 's Larsen in again . Larsen comes in with a two penny drop . He 's gonna need one .
Stedman almost into the ropes there .
[ Continues , Indistinct ]
- [ Clock Ticking ] - Darling .
What is it ?
[ Carol Breathes Erratically ]
- Don 't you feel well ? - [ Phone Rings ]
Oh I know you don 't want me to go away but —
[ Ringing Continues ]
- Hello ? - [ Man On TV Continues ]
Hello ?
[ Man On TV ] But the first point to Hunter and Larsen .
[ Cheering On TV ]
[ Man ] Fourteen and a half minutes gone .
[ Continues , Indistinct ]
[ Dog Barking In Distance ]
[ Bell Clanging ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Sister Laughs ]
[ Clanging Continues ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Clanging Stops ]
- [ Sister Laughs ] - [ Man Whispering ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Sister Moaning ]
[ Moaning Intensifies ]
[ Sighing ]
Mmm .
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Door Opens ]
- [ Faucet Squeaks ] - [ Water Running ]
- [ Water Stops ] - [ Ticking Continues ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
Why 'd you throw Michael 's things away ?
- Why 'd you do it ? - I don 't like them there .
It 's got absolutely nothing to do with you .
You silly little fool .
[ Clock Ticking ]
I 've put the money for the rent on the table .
Oh , please . Don 't go .
Now please , don 't forget to give the money ...
otherwise we shall both be out onto the street .
- Look . Are you coming or aren 't you ? - Yes , yes . I 'm coming .
Don 't look so sad .
- The time will pass very quickly . - [ Elevator Whirring ]
Don 't do anything I wouldn 't do . [ Chuckles ]
Go on .
[ Bird Chirping ]
[ Yawns ]
[ Elevator Whirring ]
[ Chirping Continues ]
[ Engine Starts ]
Oh !
- You 're killing me ! - Sorry , Miss Balch .
- There 's only — - Good morning .
Good morning . There 's only one way to deal with men .
That 's treat them as though you don 't give a damn about them .
I 've told you all this before .
Still , I 'm glad to see you have listened to me just this once .
There 's only one thing they want , and I 'll never know ...
why they make such a fuss about it , but they do .
And the more you make them beg for it , the happier they are .
- [ Bridget ] He rang me up this morning . - I said he would .
- He was practically on his knees . - Well make sure he stays that way .
I wonder , I don 't suppose it would do me any harm if I had a little snack .
Well what do you fancy ?
They 're all the same , just like children . They want to be spanked , then given sweets .
Perhaps a ...
little Danish pastry .
- Tsk , tsk . - And a cup of chocolate .
Carol will order it for you .
Carol .
Stop dreaming .
Are you feeling all right , love ?
Carol , what 's the matter ?
There 's nothing you 'd like to tell me ?
I mean , uh —
How do you feel now ?
Still biting your nails , eh ?
I think you 'd better go home . Would you like one of the girls to go with you ?
No , please . I 'll be all right .
Take a taxi anyway . Uh , ask Millie to give you the money .
Thank you .
[ Horn Honks In Distance ]
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Phone Rings ]
Hello ?
[ Man Breathing On Phone ]
[ Breathing Continues ]
Hello ?
[ Dial Tone ]
[ Handset Settles In Cradle ]
[ Bird Chirping , Faint ]
[ Chattering , Laughter , Faint ]
[ Chattering , Laughter ]
[ Razor Clinks ]
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Dripping Continues ]
[ Gags ]
[ Car Passing ]
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Rattling , Clang ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Rattling Stops ]
# [ Piano : Scales ]
# [ Piano : Discordant Note ]
# [ Scale Resumes ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Gasps Softly ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Footsteps Continue ]
- [ Door Opens ] - [ Light Switch Clicks ]
[ Glass Clinks ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Whimpers Softly ]
[ Sliding ]
[ Soft Creaking ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Water Trickling ]
# # [ Jazz Ensemble : Up-tempo ]
[ Seagulls Squawking ]
[ Squawking Continues ]
# [ Continues ]
# [ Ends ]
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Loud Crack ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Lock Clicks ]
[ Clock Ticking Softly ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Faint Footsteps ]
[ Faint Slow Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Footsteps Continue ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Footsteps Continue ]
[ Shuffling Footsteps ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Footsteps Stop ]
[ Ticking Grows Louder ]
[ Inaudible Scream ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Man ] Hello Carol ?
It 's-It 's Colin . H-Hello ?
Carol . Carol , it 's me .
[ Flies Buzzing ]
Carol . Please answer —
[ Buzzing Continues ]
[ Child Chattering In Distance ]
[ Child Shouting In Distance ]
[ Water Dripping ]
I 'm running a business here Carol , not a rest home .
You can 't just disappear for three days .
Are you sure — Well I mean , you 're not in any trouble ?
No , I 'm not . I 'm really —
But surely you could have phoned .
- Well , what is it ? - Mrs. Shaw-Taylor wants to see you .
All right . I 'll be with you in a minute .
Carol I can 't help you if you won 't tell me what 's the matter .
Oh — Well —
[ Disgusted Sigh ]
Well , one of my aunts came to stay very suddenly .
Oh . I was back at work two days after I had my first baby .
If you 're going to vanish every time a relative appears ...
we might just as well put up the shutters .
I 'd better go and see what that old bitch wants .
Now , you go back to your work . I 'll talk to you later .
And , Carol ? Do something about your hair .
Yes madame .
[ Screams ]
[ Gasps ]
- Oh my God . Look , look . - It 's nothing .
Out .
I should have your luck , getting off early .
Come on . Cheer up .
Don 't look so mis .
[ Pigeon Cooing ]
You know , you really don 't look well .
- Is it a man ? - A man ?
Well I thought that maybe that smooth boy — What 's his name ? Was making you unhappy .
You know , the one I 've seen you with .
Are you in love with him ?
I 'm not in love with anyone .
Well , what were you up to for the last three days ?
Nothing . I stayed at home .
Oh , well . That 's enough to drive anyone up the wall .
You ought to go out , go to a movie or something .
- Oh I 'd love to . - That 's it then . Do it .
We saw such a funny Chaplin film at the Classic the other night .
What was it called ? [ Laughs ]
I thought I 'd die laughing .
He was so hungry , he wanted to eat his shoe .
- No . - Yes .
He pretended the laces were spaghetti .
There was this huge great big fat man who wanted to eat him .
- What ? Him ? - Yes .
He wanted to eat Charlie Chaplin .
He thought Charlie was a chicken .
- Chicken ? - Yes .
And the chicken walked like Chaplin too .
You know .
Roger laughed so much , I was quite ashamed of him .
You ought to see it though to cheer you up .
[ Airplane Passing Overhead ]
[ Line Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
[ Horn Honks ]
Still keeping her legs crossed ?
She 's getting you down , you know .
The old old story — " Not before we 're married , darling .
I wouldn 't waste your money .
She seems a dead loss to me .
I mean , don 't let her being foreign fool you .
They 're all the same , these bloody virgins — They 're just teasers , that 's all .
She seems to have old Colin nicely steamed up though .
She gets a big thrill out of it .
You tell her . She 'll soon strip off .
- When I want your advice I 'll ask for it . - Ah .
I do believe the old lad 's in love .
- What about that then ? - Another good man gone .
I think your friends are going to have to help you .
Why don 't you , um take her over to Reggie 's pad one evening ?
Here . Steady on John .
Oh , Reggie will lay something on . Won 't you , Reggie ?
Or on something . [ Chuckling ]
I can see the scene now .
[ Metal Rattling In Distance ]
Sweet music , soft lights , a big jug of iced gin with um , orange or lemon on top of it .
- Oranges . - Why , tell her it 's a fruit cup ...
and three of the most eligible bachelors in London .
Here . " m getting excited already .
By the end of the evening , she 'll be begging for it .
- You 'll soon be able to stop twitching . - She 'll weep with gratitude .
Yeah . Maybe we will too .
- Maybe you want your face pushed in . - Here . Take your hands off me .
Colin for heaven 's sake .
Relax . Take a joke . Hit me or something .
Now , look , boy . You 've got it bad . Look .
You see ? He 's been in the sun too long .
Look , it was only a joke .
There 's no need to bloody bust out going on like Cassius Clay all over the place .
- A joke , boy . Joke . - Fellas , fellas please .
'F you go on like this you will be old before your time .
Look relax , take it easy enjoy life .
[ Spitting ]
# # [ Drums Beating ]
# [ Drums Continue ]
# [ Fades ]
[ Clock Ticking Rapidly ]
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Buzzing ]
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Rumbling Cracking ]
[ Rumbling Continues ]
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Cracking ]
[ Doorbell Rings ]
[ Colin ] Carol ?
Carol !
[ Doorbell Ringing ]
There 's somebody there . I can see your shadow .
What 's the matter ? I just want to talk to you that 's all .
Carol !
If you don 't open the door , I 'll bloody well break it down !
- No ! - What ?
[ Bangs Door ]
[ Doorknob Rattling ]
[ Rattling Continues ]
[ Retreating Footsteps ]
[ Running Footsteps ]
[ Slams Into Door ]
[ Panting ]
# [ Piano : Scales ]
I 'm sorry .
It 's all so sordid .
# [ Discordant Note ]
What 's — What 's the matter ?
I 'm sorry . I just —
Well I had to see you , that 's all .
Honestly , it 's been so — so miserable without you .
[ Elevator Whirs ]
I phoned and phoned .
The ringing tone nearly drove me mad .
[ Airplane Passing Overhead ]
Is it , uh — Is it something I 've done ?
[ Whispers ] Carol .
# [ Piano Continues ]
# [ Discordant Note , Scales Resume ]
Please .
Tell me .
[ Sighs ]
I 'm not really like this , you know .
[ Sighs ] Oh .
I wish I could find the proper words to say .
They just keep going round and round in my head .
I — I just —
I want to be — to be with you .
- All the time . - [ Dog Barking ]
- [ Thuds ] - [ Colin Groans ]
[ Hinges Squeaking ]
[ Panting ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Barking Continues ]
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Body Dragging ]
[ Clock Ticking Softly ]
# # [ Carol Vocalizing ]
# # [ Continues ]
[ Flies Buzzing ]
# # [ Voice Breaking ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Rings ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Horse-drawn Carriage Passing ]
[ Faint Footsteps ]
[ Doorbell Rings ]
[ Footsteps Departing ]
- [ Knocking On Other Door ] - [ Dog Barking ]
[ Elevator Door Opens ]
[ Elevator Whirring ]
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Ringing ]
Hello .
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Woman ] You filthy bitch .
I 'm sorry . Who is this ?
[ Mocking ] Who is this ? Who is this ?
Who do you think you filthy little tart ? You think I don 't know he 's with you ?
You think you 're clever , but you 're not that clever , you filthy —
[ Ringing ]
[ Ringing Stops ]
- # # [ Banjo ] - # # [ Rhythmic Clicking ]
# # [ Continues ]
[ Doorbell Rings ]
Come on ! Open up this door .
[ Ringing ]
Come on . Open up . I know you 're in there .
It 's no use hiding .
Else I II call the police .
[ Birds Chirping ]
[ Flies Buzzing ]
Well !
Where 's Miss Ledoux ?
I am Miss Ledoux .
You don 't look like her .
- I expect you want my sister . - Expect ?
I certainly do .
[ Buzzing Continues ]
Where is she ?
She 's not — But I can explain .
Explain ?
Well , I doubt that , my dear .
I can see it with my own eyes .
Now then what 's the idea of barricading the door against me ?
[ Woman Shouting In Distance ]
You 're not only late with the rent ...
but you 're damaging the property .
I 've got the rent here .
[ Chattering In Distance ]
Let 's have a little light on the subject .
No !
I 'm not a bloody owl , you know .
[ Woman Squealing , Shouting ]
Ah I thought I 'd seen everything .
This is a flaming nuthouse .
I don 't know .
Uh , do you always , uh ...
run around like , uh , this ?
I mean to say , it 's a bit , uh —
[ Woman Squealing In Distance ]
What 's the matter ?
You ill ?
Ah .
The , uh , heat 's getting you down , hmm ?
Uh , I don 't like it myself .
I 'll , uh — I 'll get you a — a glass of water .
You 're white as a sheet .
Hmm .
[ Gasps ]
What the hell is this ?
[ Groans ]
Oh . No wonder you look ill , if you have things like this hanging around .
It 's the dustbin for you my lad .
[ Clattering ]
[ Loud Clattering ]
Good Lord .
[ Chuckles ] Beats me how you young people live in such a mess .
It 's like a pigsty . Huh .
[ Chuckling ]
Ah . [ Chuckles ]
I know . Ah .
A nice , hot cup of tea might be better , perhaps , hmm ?
Of course , um , your sister 's gone away , hasn 't she ?
Yes uh —
A nice , hot cup of tea and , uh — and an aspirin ...
and you 'll be as right as rain .
You must be a bit lonely I expect ...
now she 's gone .
Yes I — I should have guessed it .
All alone by the telephone .
There 's uh , no need to be alone , you know .
Huh ?
Poor little girl .
All by herself .
All shaking like a little frightened animal .
Oh . Ah .
Ah .
[ Chuckles ]
[ Woman Shouts In Distance ]
They 're your family , hmm ?
Very nice . Hmm .
Yeah . There 's no need to be frightened of me , you know .
Is that you ?
[ Laughing ] Huh ?
Where was it taken ? In uh — In London ?
- Brussels . - Ah .
Ah . Brussels . Hmm .
[ Woman Laughing , Squealing ]
[ Bell Clanging ]
[ Clanging Continues ]
I could be a very good friend to you , you know .
You ... look after me ...
and you can forget about the rent .
Come on . Come on . Just —
Just a little kiss between friends , huh ? Come on .
[ Clanging Continues ]
[ Clanging Stops ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Gasps ]
# # [ Up-tempo Jazz ]
[ Groans ]
[ Groaning , Gagging ]
[ Wheezing Exhale ]
- # # [ Stops ] - [ Clock Ticking ]
# # [ Double Bass : Somber Melody ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
- # [ Continues ] - [ Ticking Continues ]
# # [ Stops ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
# [ Resumes ]
- # [ Continues ] - [ Ticking Continues ]
# [ Fades ]
# # [ Carol Vocalizing ]
# # [ Vocalizing Continues ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Bell Clanging ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Panting ]
[ Vehicle Engine Revving ]
[ Michael ] You go on up . I 'll park the car .
[ Clattering ]
Carol ?
Carol ! Are you in ?
[ Helen Screams , Gasping ]
[ Hysterical Panting ]
I say what 's the matter ?
What a terrible smell .
What the hell 's going on ? Well get a grip of yourself , will you ?
- Now , what 's the matter ? - [ Crying ]
[ Groans ] Ba — Bathroom .
[ Water Dripping ]
[ Panting ]
[ Groaning ] No ! Oh !
Go in there .
Just sit — sit there .
[ Dog Barking ]
- Have you got a phone ? - Who are you ?
I need to phone . I need to phone !
- Want a telephone ? - Yes a telephone .
Oh .
[ Dog Barks ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
Everything will be all right .
He 's gone to the porter 's room to make a telephone call .
She doesn 't speak English does she ?
[ Man ] Yes , I think she does .
[ Woman Gasps ]
[ Woman ] What 's the matter ? What 's happened ?
I don 't know . We just came in .
Let 's see . Oh .
[ Man ] Oh .
[ Dog Whimpering ]
Now , you better not touch her . They 've sent —
- [ Man ] I won 't forget tonight in a hurry . - Now come — Now don 't touch her .
I 'll get her some brandy .
- Has anyone called for an ambulance ? - Yes . He 's gone to telephone now .
- Who ? - Man we saw on the stairs .
- Ah . - Can anyone do artificial respiration ?
[ Man # 1 ] You shouldn 't touch her . You shouldn 't move her .
- [ Woman ] Oh , dear . - I 'll get her some brandy .
Somebody must help her . Please , someone help her .
[ Dog Whining ]
[ Man ] I wouldn 't touch her . Don 't touch her .
[ Woman ] What 's he doing ?
- [ Man ] Oh . - [ Woman ] Good Lord .
- [ Man ] Oh , he 's gotten her up . - Please !
He shouldn 't touch her .
[ Chattering ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Ticking Continues ]
[ Rain Pattering ]
# # [ Flute : Somber Melody ]
# [ Continues ]
# [ Ends ]